savewealth.com 2008-06-17

# SaveWealth.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  

At SaveWealth.com, we're committed to protecting your privacy. We take every visitor's personal information very seriously, and want to explain in further detail how we protect it.

**  
****What Information Do You Collect?**

When you visit our website, we archive non-identifying information, such as the type of browser you are using, the time and date of your visit, and the website that brought you to SaveWealth.com. We use this data to help us make our site more useful to visitors, based on the number of visitors and the types of technology our visitors use.

We do NOT track or record information about individuals and their visits.

When you complete any request for information, we ask for your name, address, phone number, e-mail, and a description of what you are requesting. Providing as much information as possible us to respond quickly with an answer to your questions.

**Do You Request Phone Numbers?**

Because of the nature of the subject matter discussed (namely, estate planning and retirement planning), it is often much easier to discuss your personal situation over the telephone. For this reason, we periodically will ask for your telephone number. 

You are under no obligation to provide ANY information you don't feel comfortable giving out. Providing a telephone number in most cases helps us to fulfill your request much more quickly, and provide the infomation you want faster.

**Do You Use "Cookies"?**

No. "Cookies" are bits of information stored by your browser. At SaveWealth.com, we do NOT plant any cookies on your hard drive to track your internet habits. You can use any part of the website without worrying about a cookie following you around.

**Will You Sell My Information?**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to ANY third parties, and take great measures to protect your data.

As an educational website, SaveWealth.com contracts with corporate partners to fulfill information requests. Data you provide to SaveWealth.com may be shared with a corporate partner, but ONLY if that corporation agrees to maintain our tough privacy standards, and keeps your information confidential. Your data remains secure, under lock and key at all times.

**How Will You Use My E-mail?**

E-mail is an easy and efficient way of giving you the answers you're looking for.

When you request information, you always have the option of requesting to receive periodic news on financial or estate matters via e-mail. If you do not wish to receive these regular e-mailings, it is always your choice.

If you should ever change your mind or wish to update your contact information, please [update](https://www.savewealth.com/contact/change/) us.

**What About External Links?**

Any information that you provide to parties linked from this website is maintained under that company's privacy policy. Information is not shared with SaveWealth.com by these parties. Several of our corporate partners maintain very strict guidelines to ensure your private information remains just that: **private.**

**Is Your Site Designed For Kids?**

Because of its financial subjects, SaveWealth.com is designed for mature guests over the age of 18. Because we do not ask your age, no information should be submitted to or posted at SaveWealth.com by guests under 18 years of age. 

SaveWealth.com adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and does not accept submissions from children under the age of 18. We ask for your help in respecting this policy, and keeping children's personal information protected. 

We encourage you to visit the Center for Media Education's guide to children's privacy at [www.kidsprivacy.org](http://www.kidsprivacy.org/).

**In Summary...**

Your privacy is of paramount importance. We use the information we collect to improve SaveWealth.com, and ensure you receive accurate estate planning, retirement and investing information. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SaveWealth.com. If we change this policy, we will post changes here so that you always know how we handle your private information.

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy. Please [contact us](http://www.savewealthllc.com/contact/) and tell us what you think about our privacy policy. ****
